samplelettersworld.com 2013-12-16

# SampleLettersWorld.com - Privacy Policy

---|---  
  
SampleLettersWorld.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how SampleLettersWorld.com treats personal information that SampleLettersWorld.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of SampleLettersWorld.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

## Information Collection and Use

### General

  * To continuously assess the value of our online shopping experience, we may track the way customers use our site; however, this information is analyzed only in the aggregate and not at the individual level.
  * SampleLettersWorld.com collects personal information when you register with SampleLettersWorld.com, when you use SampleLettersWorld.com products or services, when you visit SampleLettersWorld.com pages or the pages.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, Address, ZIP code. When you register with SampleLettersWorld.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * SampleLettersWorld.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of services that we offer.
  * SampleLettersWorld.com automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, SampleLettersWorld.com cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.
  * SampleLettersWorld.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and for internal reporting

### What information does SampleLettersWorld.com collect and how does it use it?

When placing an order, you will be asked to fill out and submit an online form that includes your name, telephone number, mailing address, e-mail address and credit card information. SampleLettersWorld.com uses two highly reputable and secure payment gateways to sell its products online. Our Payment Gateways have their own privacy policies:

  * Paypal

  * SecurePay

### Is my order secure?

We only work with highly reputable payment gateways. This means that your credit card information is only transmitted to this highly secure payment gateways. We do not receive any credit card information from you. Check security information for buyers when ordering through a SampleLettersWorld.com payment gateway:

Paypal Security  
Paypal Security Center

Google Checkout  
Google Checkout Security Center  
Privacy Policy  
Terms of Service

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * SampleLettersWorld.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with SampleLettersWorld.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help SampleLettersWorld.com communicate with you about offers from SampleLettersWorld.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of SampleLettersWorld.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

  * We transfer information about you if SampleLettersWorld.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, SampleLettersWorld.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  * SampleLettersWorld.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

  * SampleLettersWorld.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

## Email address?

### How do you protect my email address?

SampleLettersWorld.com does not send spam or sell email addresses. SampleLettersWorld.com has a strong history of providing excellent customer service, and our goal is to continue this tradition. With your permission, from time to time, we may notify you of special offers and/or send you online information that may be of interest to you.

### Cookies

  * SampleLettersWorld.com may set and access SampleLettersWorld.com cookies on your computer.

  * SampleLettersWorld.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to SampleLettersWorld.com's cookies.

  * SampleLettersWorld.com uses web beacons to access SampleLettersWorld.com cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with SampleLettersWorld.com products and services.

## Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

### General

  * You can edit your SampleLettersWorld.com Account Information, at any time.

  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the SampleLettersWorld.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the SampleLettersWorld.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your SampleLettersWorld.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

  * You can delete your SampleLettersWorld.com account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

### Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

  * To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please read Security at SampleLettersWorld.com.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * SampleLettersWorld.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your SampleLettersWorld.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions and Suggestions

SampleLettersWorld.com is TRUSTe-certified. This certification applies to all English-language sites under the SampleLettersWorld.com domain. If you feel that your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe, an independent privacy organization. TRUSTe serves as a liaison with SampleLettersWorld.com to resolve your concern.

#### If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at:
